Hello everyone, welcome back to another edition of This Just In.
I am joined, as always, with a dynamic duo.
The experts of the situation.
Hello everyone.
Alright, I'm joined with Marco from Italian Pod.
Hi, I am Marco from Italian Pod, and just to let you know, I was chewing a gum, but
for you guys out there, I sacrificed myself and I put it in a piece of tape.
Okay, thank you Marco.
And I am also with Leo from Spanish Pod.
I'm also sacrificed.
Hold on.
That's disgusting.
Yeah, he's taking out his gum and putting it in a piece of paper.
Thank you Leo.
What are we doing here today?
Oh, by the way, do you know, I want to finish this Marco1, Marco0 thing.
Alright, so what's going on?
So how are we going to finish this?
Well, either you're going to change your name or I'm going to change your name.
Well, I thought you were going to change your name.
You're going to change your name.
I thought you were going to be Elizabeth.
Right, but I thought that it must be...
Are we going to start with a fight again?
Could be misleading.
No, no, no, no, no.
I thought...
Okay, the final solution is we both change our names.
Okay.
Yeah, that could sound...
That could be good.
Do you have a name in mind or do you want me to choose for you?
How about I go by Mark?
Okay.
How about I go by Noodles?
Alright.
Or Egg.
Egg.
No, I like Noodles.
Noodles.
Okay, so Mark and Noodles.
Hey.
Alrighty.
What's up?
How about you go by Naboo?
Naboo, as in the planet from Star Wars?
Well, you can spell it differently if you want.
Alright, well, first let's take a look at some of the really,
really important news that I have for everyone out there.
Are they important?
They are really important.
Really important?
Really important.
Okay.
The first thing is that you are going to be able to vote
for what new show you want to listen on English pod.
Nice.
How are we going to do that?
Power to the people.
Democracy!
Okay, well, so what, where, how?
On the website, you're going to have a link of User Voice
where you go on the lesson page.
When?
You can start voting now.
Sorry, I'm a curious person.
So you can go to our lesson page and you're going to find a link
to User Voice where you can go and you're going to vote
for what show you want on English pod.
Oh, so that's what this User Voice is for.
Exactly.
So click on User Voice, go in there and vote.
We have a lot of different ideas we can have a show about.
Give us some, some preview of what are the options.
Alright, so some of the options are a show about English literature.
That sounds very interesting.
We have a show, a cultural show.
It is, it is.
A cultural show about, for example, American culture,
British culture, or many different English speaking countries.
Like Canadian culture.
Canadian, yeah, fish and chips, yeah, all that stuff.
Irish.
Exactly.
And we also have a show about how to do things, the how to show.
Oh, the how to show.
Isn't that like a Discovery Channel show?
Is it really?
But I think the cool thing is that you learn language
and you learn a practical skill, appliance of the language.
Yeah.
Can I say appliance, Martin?
No, application.
Thank you.
You see?
Oh, this is the only English pod.
Wow, I cannot stop learning with this.
So we have a couple of different ideas.
Even there's an idea for having kind of a lyrics show.
Like a music show.
Right, so we would play a clip of one of your favorite songs
and we could maybe try and explain some of the difficult words
or what that sentence means.
Or listen to this.
Just had this idea, guys.
Lyrics and every time we listen to the song
and we have to sing it ourselves.
Yeah, that could work as well.
Like who ourselves?
You.
Like Leo.
Do you want me to sing?
Yes, if we pick a song.
And every time that we analyze the chorus,
then you sing the chorus of the song.
We can try it now with...
La Bamba.
Bravo, bravisio.
All right, I love this.
Can we vote for the shows or we don't?
Yeah, you can vote.
Yeah?
Or we can vote for who do they want to sing?
Marco Uno, Marco Los.
I think we should all take turns.
Anyway, so everybody that is a user can vote.
Everybody can vote.
And so whichever show gets the highest amount of votes,
we'll start doing it.
You know, I've always been thrilled about this song, Thriller.
Can you sing a bit of Thriller?
Yeah, like I don't understand why.
What? What did you just say?
I mean, there's like monsters in the video club, isn't it?
Yeah.
Well, if you vote for the show and the show win,
maybe we can explain to you all the stuff.
Maybe we can create our own video
and all of us will dance to Thriller.
Don't say that.
Because now that people are going to push for it,
they will have to.
Well, if they push for it, we'll do it.
Don't push for it.
And Marco will be heading in.
Okay, just one thing though.
If you're voting, please do not go and click 1,000 times
from the same computer because that's not fair.
That's not nice, right?
No, let's keep it legal.
It has to be fair.
All right.
And another exciting news.
Now you can add EnglishPod as a friend on Facebook.
EnglishPod now has a page on Facebook.
So we're going to be posting pictures, videos,
and we're even going to be having contests
and different news on Facebook.
So in this way, you can interact more with us.
Is it true that the EnglishPod on Facebook
states as relationship status, it's complicated?
What does that mean?
No, no, no, that does not exist.
Can I be like EnglishPod and Leonardo,
they are in a relationship?
Yeah, it's like...
Okay, the user of the month...
Could get a relationship.
Will be able to be in a relationship,
unless he's already in a relationship
with EnglishPod for a month.
How about that, guys?
Well, anyways, I've posted also a link on the lesson page
so you can follow it and become a fan of EnglishPod.
It'll be really cool
because we'll be posting different stuff
and we'll have competitions
and also you can meet other people,
so it'll be nice.
To the first 100 people
who joined the Facebook page of EnglishPod as a fan,
we will throw in Marco Zero,
AKA Naboo's phone number.
You can call him anytime
and ask English-related question
or not only English-related question.
All right, all right.
We can do that.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll give him Leo's number.
All right.
The first one,
we have Marco as a slave for a day.
All right, so...
So what about the lesson?
Lessons coming out next week.
We have a lesson about being in an airplane.
Okay.
So...
Wow.
Great, like on a cargo plane or on a...
No, no, no.
We're in a passenger plane
and you know how the captain always comes on
and goes like...
Oh, yeah.
This is your captain speaking.
Oh, I have a theory about that.
What's your theory?
I have a theory that he's not saying anything at all
because I've never been able to figure out what he says.
He says like 26 degrees,
then he says cloudy,
then he says like...
Shanghai?
Yeah, Shanghai and have a good journey.
It's like this.
I'm taking for a flight with him.
Yeah, no.
Don't give him a flight with him.
Cloudy?
No, sorry.
27 degrees,
then he says, you know,
Shanghai.
Lovely, like that.
That's what we'll do like that.
Is it true or no?
We're going to do our just Shanghai...
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Rehears the beam.
You know how much I pay for this flight.
Oh, yeah, what a good service.
All right.
Well, in this lesson,
we're going to be able to now understand
what the captain is really saying.
Oh, I have to listen to this.
Yeah, you should.
We have the lesson coming out on Wednesday
is the first part of three of the job interview series.
That's useful.
Wow, so you're going to explain
how to be successful in a job interview?
Exactly.
Wow.
In three parts.
You're not just learning English.
You're learning how to get a job
in this financial crisis time.
Yeah, exactly.
So now we're going to be able to give you
the tools for a successful job interview,
which is really important.
So you can dream about getting a job.
Exactly.
And Friday's lesson,
it's part four of the new guy in town.
Is this one of the soap operas?
Yeah, it's kind of like the vampire guy, right?
Yeah, the vampire guy.
But now there's it's a very,
very different twist to the story.
So you've got to listen
because it's completely different.
Yeah, so what's going to happen?
And to finish off our show,
the user of the week.
All right.
Where is he from?
Oh, is he Mexican again?
No.
It's July from China.
July, congratulations.
Is this the user of the month of July?
Okay.
So the user of the week is July.
She's been really active on the website.
She's...
Grandma July.
July is the user of the month of March.
User of the week.
How is this the week?
The users of the week.
And well, she actually works pretty hard
from what I understand.
And she tries to find time
to listen to English pods.
So she'll be off the site
for a couple of days,
but then she'll come back on
and listen to all the lessons.
Tack!
Come on.
And she'll listen to the lesson.
So good job, July.
Keep it up.
And we're really happy to have you.
You want to say something
in Chinese to July?
I know, Marco, that you are
starting to learn Chinese.
Yeah, he's starting Chinese.
Come on, Marco.
This is July's revenge.
Come on.
What can I say?
Why are you blushing?
Because I can't say anything in Chinese.
Come on.
Yes, you can.
Lesson one.
All right.
Ni hao, July.
Bravo, Marco!
User of the week on Chinese parties.
Marco, me fia ike na bu, bravo.
You know what?
They should have user
of the week on Chinese.
They don't?
I don't think they do.
They're boring.
I'm over.
Oh, no.
I'm always there.
I've never been chosen user of the week.
Well, maybe because you work here.
Maybe.
Maybe that has to do with that.
You can be employee of the month if you want.
All right.
So that's all for today, guys.
Be sure to go to our website.
Be sure to go to UserVoice.
Vote for the new show that's coming out.
And Facebook.
Facebook.
Add us as friends on Facebook
because we're going to have a competition
on Facebook coming out this week.
That's soon.
Yes.
So no time to lose.
No time to lose.
So be sure to go to Facebook,
come to our website,
and we'll see you guys there.
I'm going to poke Englishbot now.
Yeah, you can poke us on Facebook.
Enough with the poking.
Let's have sex, Englishbot.
All right.
So that's all for today.
We'll see you guys next time.
Later.
Bye.
Ciao.
Englishbot.com.